

NATALIA IANCOVSCAIA

iancovscaia.natalia.alexandr@gmail.com +467 33449633

SanktKnutsTorg 3A Malmö

EDUCATION

Front-End Development

Medicinstitutet
2024 Applied mathematics

State University of Moldova
2000-2004

SKILLS

- Strong ability to work with large amounts of data and document management systems.
- Excellent problem-solving skills, with extensive experience in technical support.
- Rapid learning of new technologies, frameworks, and software tools.
- Strong communication and interpersonal skills.
- Creative thinking and accuracy in project execution
- Programming: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,
 Node.js, WebSocket,React

LANGUAGE

- English
- Swedish
- Romanian
- Russian

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic person with a strong background in technical support, data processing and troubleshooting. Experience in handling large amounts of data, providing technical assistance via phone and email, and ensuring smooth delivery of products and services. Quick to adapt to new technologies and tools, with a strong problem-solving mindset and the ability to think creatively in fast-paced environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Juni 2004– April 2019 SRLDitaEstFarm(Pharmaceutical Wholesale Warehouse), Moldova

Technical Operator

Processed up to 1000 invoices daily and handled over 3000 pharmaceutical products. Fixed and resolved software input errors to ensure operational continuity. Finding solutions to problems Provided customer support via phone and email, managed over 160 pharmacies and store accounts.

April 2019 – Juni 2021 SRL United Vision (Optical Warehouse), Moldova Operator

Managed inventory of optical products, including lenses, frames, and lens pflege products from brands such as Bausch and Cooper.

Ensured high product quality and customer satisfaction through careful product management. Processed invoices and consignment notes, and maintained an organized and accurate inventory system.

www.linkedin.com/in/natalia-iancovscaia-95b1a8223

https://github.com/NataliaIancovscaia